Guide to the Charles H. Long, Deputy Provost, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Charles H. Long, deputy provost, Yale University, records
1968-2011
RU 1074
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
17.75
(20 boxes)
The records consist of correspondence, reports, committee files, meeting minutes, and subject files maintained by Charles H. Long as deputy provost of Yale University.
Yale University. Office of the Provost
Long, Charles Howard
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 3-B (YRG 3-B), Records of Yale deputy, associate, and assistant provosts.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The records were transferred from the Office of the Provost, 2008-2010 and 2016.
Conditions Governing Access
Restricted until January 1, 2047
Biographical / Historical
The Office of the Provost was created by vote of the Yale Corporation in 1919. The establishment of the office was part of a general University reorganization plan that was submitted to the Corporation by the Committee on Educational Policy. By the term of Provost Edgar S. Furniss (1937-1958), the office had evolved to essentially its present-day function. The provost is the chief academic officer of the University, responsible for administering all of the internal operations of the University concerned with education and research.
Biographical / Historical
Charles Long was Deputy Provost of the University from 1987 to 2010. He came to Yale in 1966, and after a number of years on the faculty of the English Department, moved to the Yale College Dean's Office where he eventually became Dean of Academic Affairs. He later was appointed to the Provost's Office, where he has been since 1983, becoming Deputy Provost of the University in 1987. During his years in the Provost's Office, Deputy Provost Long's responsibilities included many academic departments and a wide variety of professional schools including oversight of many of the Humanities and Social Science departments of the Faculty of Arts and Sciences, the professional schools of Law and Management, and the University's core academic policies. His portfolio also included the MacMillan Center for International and Area Studies and the Center for the Study of Globalization.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of correspondence, reports, committee files, meeting minutes, and subject files maintained by Charles H. Long as deputy provost of Yale University.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by accession.
Universities and colleges -- Administration; Yale University -- Administration; Yale University. Office of the Provost
- Records, 1970-2006; Accession 2008-A-151
  - Affirmative action - Grievances
  - Affirmative Action - General
    - Admission Procedure, 1990 February 5 - 1996 June 3 (Box 4, Folder 141)
    - Plan Summary, 1990- 2000 (Box 4, Folder 142)
    - Statemen, 1995-1996 (Box 4, Folder 143)
    - African American Statistics, 2001 August 31 - 2002 August 31 (Box 4, Folder 144)
    - Age Discrimination, 1979 June 12 - October 24 (Box 4, Folder 145)
    - Early Background
      - 1970 Apr 20 - 1981 Dec 9 (Box 4, Folder 146)
      - 1971 Sep 9 - 1980 Oct 15 (Box 4, Folder 147)
    - Black Women in Academe, 1989 August (Box 4, Folder 148)
    - Budget, 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 149)
    - AA Bulletins, 1983-2004 (Box 4, Folder 150 - 152)
    - AA Bulletins: Other Universities, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 153)
    - Child Care
      - Analysis, 1990 June (Box 4, Folder 154)
      - General, 1985 September 20 - 1993 June 17 (Box 4, Folder 157)
      - Instituttional Survey, 1986 October 16 - 1990 February 20 (Box 4, Folder 158)
      - Supplement, 1987 April (Box 4, Folder 159)
    - Cofhe Survey, 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 160)
    - Complaint Process Audit, 2002 April (Box 4, Folder 161)
    - Compliance Action, 1984-1991 (Box 4, Folder 162)
    - Compliance Officer, 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 163)
    - Yale Corporation files [restricted 50 years from date of creation]
      - Reports
        - 2003-2004 (Box 4, Folder 166)
        - 2001-2002 (Box 4, Folder 167)
        - 1999-2000 (Box 4, Folder 168)
        - EPC, 1999-2000 (Box 4, Folder 169)
        - 1998-1999 (Box 4, Folder 170)
        - EPC, 1997-1998 (Box 4, Folder 171)
        - 1994-1995 (Box 4, Folder 172)
        - 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 173 - 174)
        - 1992-1993 (Box 4, Folder 175)
        - EPC, 1992-1993 (Box 4, Folder 176)
        - 1990-1991 (Box 4, Folder 177)
        - IPC Minority Faculty Report, 1994-1995 (Box 4, Folder 178)
    - Crothers Report on Education of Women, 1984 April (Box 5, Folder 179)
    - Crothers Report to the Faculty, 1985 April (Box 5, Folder 180)
    - Employment of Women and Members of Racial/Ethnic Minority Groups, 2000-2001 (Box 5, Folder 181)
    - E.O.P. Office (Equal Opportunity Program), 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 182)
    - Faculty, 1998-1999 (Box 5, Folder 183)
    - Faculty Appointments, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 184)
    - Faculty Diversity Initiative, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 185)
    - Faculty: Psychology Search, 1998-1999 (Box 5, Folder 186)
    - Faculty Statistics, 1990-1991 (Box 5, Folder 187)
    - Faculty Statistics, 1989-1990 (Box 5, Folder 188)
    - Faculty Statistics: Prior to 1989, 1986-1987 (Box 5, Folder 189)
    - General, 1980-1999 (Box 5, Folder 190)
    - Harvard Study, 1999-2000 (Box 5, Folder 195)
    - Harvard Study: Administrators, 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 196)
    - Harvard Survey
      - Faculty, 1988-1994 (Box 5, Folder 197)
      - Minority Faculty, 1993-1999 (Box 5, Folder 198)
      - University Wide, 1996-1999 (Box 5, Folder 199 - 200)
    - Jaynes Committee, 1992-1994 (Box 5, Folder 201 - 202)
    - Jaynes CTTE Report, 1990-1991 (Box 5, Folder 203)
      - President's Response, 1990-1991 (Box 5, Folder 204)
    - Jaynes Recruitment and Retention Committee, 1990-1991 (Box 5, Folder 205 - 206)
    - Lesbian/Gay Students, 1980-1988 (Box 5, Folder 207)
    - Maternity/Childcare Policies, 1990-1991 (Box 5, Folder 208)
    - Maternity Leaves-Institutional Surveys, 1987-1989 (Box 5, Folder 209)
    - Minority Asmissions Statistics, 1982-1987 (Box 5, Folder 210)
    - Minority Policy-Faculty, 1991-1996 (Box 5, Folder 211)
    - Minority Advisory Council, 1979-1993 (Box 5, Folder 212 - 213)
    - Minority Faculty, 1987-1999 (Box 5, Folder 214 - 217)
    - Minority Faculty: Statistics, 1982-1994 (Box 5, Folder 218)
    - Minority Faculty: Issues, 2001-2002 (Box 5, Folder 219)
    - Minority Faculty: Employment of Women and Minority Group Members
      - 1998-1999 (Box 5, Folder 220)
      - 2000-2001 (Box 5, Folder 221)
    - Family and Medical Leaves Act, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 222)
    - Medical School, 1987-1994 (Box 5, Folder 223)
    - Medical School: Women's Salaries, 1991-1992 (Box 5, Folder 224)
    - Princeton Report on Women in Science, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 225)
    - Old Reports, 1976-1986 (Box 5, Folder 226)
    - Racial and Ethnic Harassment Procedures, 1981-1985 (Box 6, Folder 228 - 229)
    - Reports, 1993-1994 (Box 6, Folder 230)
    - Report to Yale College Faculty, 1985 May (Box 6, Folder 231)
    - Report: FAS and Sciences Advisory Committee On the Education of Women, 1984 April (Box 6, Folder 232)
    - Rodin Committee, 1988-1991 (Box 6, Folder 233 - 236)
    - Rodin Report: President's Response, 1990 January (Box 6, Folder 237)
    - Resourse Office: General, 1994-1995 (Box 6, Folder 238)
    - Searches, 2000-2001 (Box 6, Folder 239)
    - Sexual Harassment
      - 1993-1994 (Box 6, Folder 240)
      - 1992-1993 (Box 6, Folder 241)
      - Background, 1979-1990 (Box 6, Folder 242)
      - Definition, 1987-1990 (Box 6, Folder 243)
      - Consenual Relations, 1992-1999 (Box 6, Folder 244)
      - OCR Guidelines, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 246)
      - Training, 1993-1994 (Box 6, Folder 247)
      - Medical School, 1985-1987 (Box 6, Folder 248)
    - Spousal Employment and Benefits, 1987-1988 (Box 6, Folder 249)
    - Tuesday Connection, 1990-1993 (Box 6, Folder 250)
    - Tribunal University, 1994 January (Box 6, Folder 251)
    - Women, 1982-1989 (Box 6, Folder 252)
    - Women (FAS), 1995-2001 (Box 6, Folder 253)
    - Women (FAS): 50% or more time, 1993-1994 (Box 6, Folder 254)
    - Women in Staff and Faculty Positions, 2003-2004 (Box 6, Folder 258)
    - Women in Medicine, 1984-1988 (Box 6, Folder 259)
    - Women in Science, 1983-1986 (Box 6, Folder 260)
    - Women Faculty Task Force, 1994-1995 (Box 6, Folder 261)
      - Yale Women's Organization, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 262)
  - Faculty of Arts and Sciences (FAS) Steering Committee, 1997-2003
    - 2002 Jul 1 - 2003 Jun 30 (Box 7, Folder 263)
    - 2001 Jul 1 - 2002 Jun 30 (Box 7, Folder 264)
    - 2000 Jul 1 - 2001 Jun 30 (Box 7, Folder 265)
    - 2000 Jul 1 - Dec 31 (Box 7, Folder 266)
    - 2000 Jan 1 - Jun 30 (Box 7, Folder 267)
    - 1999 Jul 1 - 2000 Jun 30 (Box 7, Folder 268)
    - 1999 Jul 1 - Dec 31 (Box 7, Folder 269)
    - 1999 Jan 1 - Mar 31 (Box 7, Folder 270)
    - 1999 Apr 1 - Jun 30 (Box 7, Folder 271)
    - 1998 Jul 1 - Dec 31 (Box 7, Folder 272)
    - 1998 Jan 1 - Jun 30 (Box 7, Folder 273)
    - 1997 Jul 1 - Dec 31 (Box 7, Folder 274)
    - 1997 Jan 1 - Jun 30 (Box 7, Folder 275)
    - 1996 Jul 1 - Dec 31 (Box 8, Folder 276)
    - 1995 Jul 1 - 1996 Jun 30 (Box 8, Folder 277)
  - PROVOST STAFF AGENDA
    - Provost Staff Agenda, 1992-1998 (Box 8, Folder 278)
- Foundation and academic department records, 1968-2005; Accession 2009-A-119
  - Academic Departments
    - American Studies, 2003-2005 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - American Studies, 2001-2003 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - American Studies ERM Ethnic Studies (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Ethnic Studies ERM # 3, 1992-1996 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Ethnic Studies ERM # 1, 1988-1990 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Ethnic Studies: Asian American Studies (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Economics (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Economics, 2003-2005 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Economics, 2001-2003 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - English Department, 2003-2005 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - English Department, 2001-2003 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Expository Writing, 1997-2003 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Philosophy, 2003-2004 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Philosophy, 2001-2003 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Political Science, 2003-2004 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Political Science, 2002-2003 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Bass Writing Program (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Environmental Studies (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Mellon Foundation
    - Mellon General, 1998-2000 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Mellon Foundation General PAST (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Mellon General PAST, 1997-1998 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Mellon Humanist Faculty 19720, 1981-1985 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Humanist - Young - Mellon - 32434, 1978-1987 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Mellon Foundation: Report, 2000 March (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Minority Undergraduate Fellowship Program, 1988-1996 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - West European Studies, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Portable Graduate Fellowships, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Graduate School Survey, 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - Professorship - Paul Mellon, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - Residential Colleges Education Program, 1983-1996 (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - Term Chairs, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - 1974 Young Humanist 05265 (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - General, 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - Mellon Fellows Program, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - 1989 Report, 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - Special Programs Grant - Mellon 1989 Final Report, 1980-1989 (Box 1, Folder 43)
    - Departmental Requests - Mellon, 1980s (Box 1, Folder 44)
    - Mellon Foundation - Minority Program, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 45)
    - Old Dominion, 1995-1998 (Box 2, Folder 46)
    - Old Dominion Origins, 1968-1996 (Box 2, Folder 47)
    - 32424, 1980-1988 (Box 2, Folder 48 - 54)
    - Special Programs - Mellon Y/E, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 55)
    - Special Programs - Mellon, 1985 July (Box 2, Folder 56)
    - 32425, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 57)
    - Mellon Origins, 1977-1980 (Box 2, Folder 58)
    - Mellon Foundation 32432, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 59)
    - Mellon 32424, 1979-1984 (Box 2, Folder 60)
    - Mellon Literature Major 32422, 1979-1984 (Box 2, Folder 61)
    - Other Programs, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 62)
    - Original and General New Teaching and Research - 33460, 1983-1991 (Box 2, Folder 63)
    - I.S.P.S. Fellowships, 1983-1989 (Box 2, Folder 64)
    - Reports, 1990-1991 (Box 2, Folder 65)
    - Mellon Fellows, 1990-1992 (Box 2, Folder 66)
    - Mellon Reports, 1989 May - 1989 June (Box 2, Folder 67)
    - Annual Report, 2000-2001 (Box 2, Folder 68)
    - BSC Letters, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 69)
    - British Studies, 2004-2005 (Box 2, Folder 70)
    - Mellon - Clare Fellowship, 1988-1989 (Box 2, Folder 71)
    - Common Wealth of Letters (Michael Cooke), 1988-1993 (Box 2, Folder 72)
    - Directed Studies Endowment, 1988 June (Box 2, Folder 73)
    - Mellon Report: Asian Studies, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 74)
    - East Asian Studies - Mellon Endowment - 12034, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 75)
    - East Asian Studies - Mellon Endowment - 12030, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 76)
- Records, 1978-2005; Accession 2010-A-021
  - Whitney Humanities, 1996-2005 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - School of Management, 1997-1998 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - School of Management, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 3-5)
  - School of Management, 1992-1993 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Parliamentary History Papers, 1991-1993 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - School of Management, 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - School of Management, 1996-1997 (Box 1, Folder 9-10)
  - History (CHL), 1995-1998 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - History (Continued), 1997-2002 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - History (CHL): Past, 1989-1995 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Sociology: Rebuilding, 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Expository Writing, 1986-1990 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Bass Expository Writing Program, 1986-1997 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Expository Writing: Pew General, 1990-1998 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Chronological and faculty records, 1975-2008; Accession 2010-A-097
  - Chronological files
    - July 1, 1985 – June 30, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 1-2)
    - July 1, 1986 – June 30, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 3-4)
    - July 1, 1987 – June 30, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 5-6)
    - July 1, 1988 – June 30, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 7-8)
    - July 1, 1989 – June 30, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 9-10)
    - July 1, 1990 – June 30, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 11-12)
    - July 1, 1991 – June 30, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 13-14)
    - July 1, 1992 – June 30, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 15-16)
    - July 1, 1993 – June 30, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - July 1, 1994 – June 30, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - July 1, 1995 – June 30, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - July 1, 1996 – June 30, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 20-21)
    - July 1, 1997 – June 30, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 22-23)
    - July 1, 1998 – June 30, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - July 1, 1999 – June 30, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - July 1, 2000 – June 30, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - July 1, 2001 – June 30, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - July 1, 2002 – June 30, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - July 1, 2003 – June 30, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - July 1, 2004 – June 30, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - July 1, 2005 – June 30, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - July 1, 2006 – June 30, 2007 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - July 1, 2007 – June 30, 2008 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Faculty records
    - Retirement: Lang, Serge, 1978-2004 (Box 3, Folder 34-39)
- Records, 1974-2011; Accession 2017-A-045
  - Mac Millian Center
    - General files
      - 1997-1998 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      - 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 2)
      - 1999-2000 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      - 2001-2002 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      - 2002-2004 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      - 2005-2006 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Yale Center for International Area Studies (YCIAS)
      - General, 2002-2005 (Box 1, Folder 7)
      - Professorships, 2001-2002 (Box 1, Folder 8)
      - South Africian Research Program, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Academic Council on the United Nations System, 2001-2002 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - African Studies Council, 2000-2009 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Africian Languages, 1994- (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Africian Studies, 1999-2006 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Agrarian Studies, 1989-2011 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Appointments, 1996-2001 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Appointments Procedures for Visiting Teaching Research Scholars, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Budget Current, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Canadian Studies, 1983-2006 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Cities Globalization, 2002-2003 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Crossing Borders, 1998-2002 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Fox Fellowship Program, 2003-2004 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Genocide Studies Program, 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Hellenic Studies, 2003-2007 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Internationalization Of Yale, 2003-2007 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Latin America Studies Council, 2000-2003 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Latin American Council Mellon, 2003-2007 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Middle East Council, 2005-2007 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Morocco Initiative, 2009 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - North Africian Studies, 2009 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Program on Non-Profit Organizations (PONPO), 2004 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Intiative for the Interdisciplinary Study of Antisemitism (YIISA), 2010 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Political Theory Social Thought, 1987-1989 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Social Thoughts and Ethics, 1988-1992 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Social Thoughts and Ethics, 1992-1993 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Social Thoughts and Ethics, 1989-2003 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - LUCE Professorship, 1989-2000 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - LUCE International Center, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Institute for Social and Policy Studies (ISPS), 1984-2006 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Far East Publications, 1996-2000 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - International Security Studies (ISS)
    - General files
    - 1989-2001 (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - 2001-2003 (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - 2004-2006 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Grand Strategy, 2006-2007 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Expository Writing, 1984-1986 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Tuition Plan, 1998-2004 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - French In Action, 1989-1999 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - French in Action Annenberg Project, 1985-1988 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - French in Action Controversy, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Graduate Employees and Student Organization (GESO) Labor Relations, 1995-1996 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Johnson Edition (The Works of Samuel Johnson), 1996-2000 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Journal of Criticism, 1986-2006 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Standing Committee on Retirement
    - Phased retirement, 1978-1999 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Retirement documents, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Retirement issues
      - 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 10)
      - 1993 (Box 2, Folder 11)
      - 1996-1997 (Box 2, Folder 12)
      - 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 13)
      - 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 14)
      - 1999-2000 (Box 2, Folder 15)
      - 1999-2002 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Faculty retirement, 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Working group report, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Crothers Committee on Retirement
      - 1988-1989 (Box 2, Folder 19-20)
      - 1989-1990 (Box 2, Folder 21)
      - Final report, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Reports and memoranda, 1990-1999 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Committee reports, 1990-1996 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Retirement reports, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Report to the Corporation, 1998 June (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Memoranda, policies and issues
      - 1974-1979 (Box 2, Folder 27)
      - 1989-1990 (Box 2, Folder 28)
      - 1990-1993 (Box 2, Folder 29)
      - 1996 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Film Studies Program Proposal on Film Studies major, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Brodkin Archive, 2005-2006 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Boswell Project Editorial Committee, 2001-2005 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Boswell Papers, 1993-2010 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Boswell Papers, 1996-1997 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Boswell Papers, 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Boswell Papers, 1999-2000 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Globalization Studies
    - Correspondence
      - 1999-2001 (Box 3, Folder 5)
      - 2001-2002 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Betts House classroom space, 2001-2008 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Budgets, 2000-2003 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Globalization Study Center
      - MacArthur Grant, 2001-2002 (Box 3, Folder 13)
      - Rockefeller Grant, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 14)
      - Yale Global Online Magazine, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Holocaust Archive, 1996-1998 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Language Consortium, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Language Consortium, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Media Design Director Search, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 20-21)
  - Mortgage Program, 2002-2009 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Murphy Professorship, 1982-1985 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Parliamentary History
    - 1991-1998 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - 1998-1999 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - 2005-2006 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - 2006-2007 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - 2007-2008 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - 2008 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Yale Review
    - Financial Support, 1998-2001 (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - Reviews
      - 1988-1989 (Box 3, Folder 32)
      - 1990-1991 (Box 3, Folder 33)
      - 1991-1994 (Box 3, Folder 34)
      - 1994-1995 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Law School
    - General files
      - 2003-2006 (Box 3, Folder 36)
      - 2007-2008 (Box 3, Folder 37)
      - 2008-2009 (Box 3, Folder 38)
      - 2009-2010 (Box 3, Folder 39)
    - Budget
      - Budget Accord, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 40)
      - Budgets
        - 1998 (Box 3, Folder 41)
        - 2007-2008 (Box 3, Folder 42)
        - 2008-2009 (Box 3, Folder 43)
        - 2010-2011 (Box 3, Folder 44)
    - China Law Center, 2006-2007 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Post Graduate Loan Repayment (COAP) surveys, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Law School Deans Preface, Undated (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Endowment discussions, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Legal Affairs, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Long range planning
      - 1996-1997 (Box 4, Folder 8)
      - 1997-1998 (Box 4, Folder 9)
      - 1998-2000 (Box 4, Folder 10)
      - 2000-2002 (Box 4, Folder 11)
      - 2006-2007 (Box 4, Folder 12)
      - Presentation, April 2005 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Loan Program Implementation, 1987-1990 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Retirement Policies, 2009 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Retirement Committee, 2006-2007 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Deans M, 1997-2007 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Staff, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Space, 1988-2006 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Swing Dorm Plans, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Tweedy Professorship, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - School of Management
    - General files
      - 1993-1999 (Box 5, Folder 7)
      - 1998-1999 (Box 5, Folder 8)
      - 1999-2001 (Box 5, Folder 9)
      - 2001-2005 (Box 5, Folder 10)
      - 2005-2006 (Box 5, Folder 11)
      - 2006-2007 (Box 5, Folder 12)
      - 2009-2010 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Appointments Procedures, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Long range planning
      - 1999-2000 (Box 6, Folder 2)
      - 2000-2001 (Box 6, Folder 3)
      - 2001-2002 (Box 6, Folder 4)
      - 2002-2003 (Box 6, Folder 5)